Hi, my name is Dave Andrews.
Today I'm going to tell you how to turn off calendar reminders in Microsoft Outlook.
Let's begin by opening up Outlook by clicking on the start button on the bottom.
Go into all programs, under Microsoft Office, let's select Outlook.
Now that we're in Outlook, let's go to tools and options and on this default reminder check box under calendar, it's by default it's checked with a reminder of fifteen minutes.
Just un-check it, and that turns off the default reminder to be set for all new calendar entries.
Select apply.
Let's open up our calendar and create a new item today at eleven o'clock.
You'll notice that the reminder at the top is set to "none".
Since we un-checked that check box, they will all be none from now on.
As you can see, it's very easy to turn off calendar reminders in Microsoft Outlook.
My name is Dave Andrews and I've just showed you how to turn off calendar reminders in Microsoft Outlook.